Yeah
Is Mrs Fu really coming
The Chairman personally asked for her
Of course she is
Does she understand projects of this scale
We'll find out soon enough
Morning Chenzhou, Mrs Fu
Morning
Must have been a long night, Mrs Fu
Fu Group's projects involve tons of files
They aren't as simple as outside ones
It's indeed not simple
That's why I read all night
This is Fu Group's key focus this year
An industrial upgrade project we are pushing
Chenzhou, you just returned to Fu Group
Today you'll mainly be sitting in
Feel free to ask if there's anything you don't get
Yeah Chenzhou is young and promising
It's always good to learn more
Fu Group's major projects are highly complex
Unlike those localized ones outside
The risks will be different
Let's hear it out first
Okay then I'll continue